(Sheldon:)- Based on the content...
- I couldn't be less interested.
(Howard:)Now, come on, I'll take you home.
- Don't you want to know what's in it?
- Lf I did, I would've opened it years ago.
(Howard:)The closet looks great.
Let's get out of here.
(Sheldon:)Can I bring this box of extra shirt buttons
to sort on the ride?
- Do whatever you want.
- Thanks.
Oh!
(Sheldon:)Great party.
When I first met Howard, he'd pull
his scrotum out of his shorts and say:
"Oh! I sat in gum."
(Penny:)What is your point?
It's kind of weird how grown up he is now.
Happily married, throwing dinner parties.
(Penny:)Really? You couldn't just say that?
You had to tell the scrotum story?
(Leonard:)Trying to paint a picture.
(Penny:)It was a nice change of pace,
not eating takeout around a coffee table.